Let's take a look at what we used to believe and then contrast it to what we now know.
我们来看看曾经被认为是正确的理念，并对比如今我们的看法
One of the biggest fallacies was believing that startups
最大的错误之一，就是认为创业公司
are just smaller versions of a large company.
乃缩小版的大公司
That everything you do in a large company, you'll do on day one of a startup.
即是大公司里的每项分工，从一开始就会照样复制到创业公司
What we now know is something very different.
我们现在的看法大不相同
The core difference is that startups do something called search
关键的不同是，创业公司主要做探索和开发
while large companies spend their time, at least their core time, executing.
而大公司主要把时间花在执行上
One of the questions we'll answer is search for what and execute what.
问题之一是探索开发什么、执行什么，我们待会儿来谈
And so later on in this lecture, you'll see the difference
在后面的课程，你会看到它们的区别
and then in fact will make you a much better enterpreneur.
到时候，我们会使你成为一个更优秀的创业者